Good afternoon I am from Ukraine, the city of
Добрый день Я из Украины город
Khmelnitsky Yes, I understand there is What is your
Хмельницкого Да я понял есть Как ваш
channel called
канал называется
our channel is not called anything I just
наш канал никак не называется Я просто
swell I am a blogger talking about the war with the
побухиваю я блогер общаюсь про войну с
Russians Yes please If you want
россиянами Да пожалуйста Если хотите
you can How do you support the war in
можем вы Как вы поддерживаете войну в
Ukraine firstly I do not support the war
Украине во-первых я не поддерживаю войну
but  supporting our Let's honestly
а поддерживая сво Давайте будем честного
scary dance No, we can
страшно танцевать Нет мы можем как
call a table whatever you like and this chair
угодно называть столом и от этого стул
will not become a table If you can call it a war
стол не станет Если можно назвать войной
from this
от этого
The fact is that we still have not
Дело в том что у нас до сих пор не
declared war on Ukraine and so Ukraine has not
объявлена война Украине и так Украина не
declared war on Russia
объявлял войну России
and we  there are partnerships which
и у нас есть партнерские отношения какие
partnerships have
партнерские
gone out which partnerships you have in terms of gas and
погас Какие по газу по газу и по
transportation and gas
транспортировке и по газу вас
you have
партнерские отношения у вас у вас
specifically you have Russia with Ukraine
конкретно у вас вот у России с Украины
what partnerships since we
Какие партнерские отношения так как мы
transport through the gas
транспортируем через газовый
transport system and pay a
транспортную систему и платим за это
lot of taxes for it  that is, to whom are you
большие деньги налоги то есть а кому вы
transporting
транспортируете
Europe Europe relations
Европа Европе отношения
Well, yes They are still relations with Europe,
Ну да Они до сих пор с Европой отношения
but
но почему
why  don’t argue now war and
давайте сейчас не спорить война и
their bastard will be you you will support this of
[__] их будет вас вы поддержите это
course you
конечно
wanted super for a year And when you go
года хотел супер А когда вы в Туле идете
to the military registration and enlistment office in Tula you have already announced
в военкомат у вас уже объявлена
partial mobilization for everyone who wants
частичная мобилизация для всех желающих
to fight in Ukraine
воевать в Украине
but it’s almost finished already And why did
но она почти закончили уже А почему вы
n’t you go That’s specifically you  I would not be a category
не пошли Вот конкретно вы я категория бы
yet,
я пока не могу
look if we are talking about mobilization,
смотри если мы говорим про мобилизацию
she is the
она
first category, she went That is, those
первая категория она пошла То есть те
who
кто
knew this are all there, let’s say they all
знали это все там допустим это все
do it And in short, all things are category B This is the
делают И короче все дела категория B Это
third wave
третья волна
That is, I am a Medic, look now
То есть я Медиков вот смотрите сейчас
Medic can Volunteers to doctors  go
Медика можно Добровольцы медикам поехать
If you support your
Если вы так поддерживаете своего
medics like that, you don’t need to get injured, your
медики не нужны ранения не получают Ваши
guys aren’t there enough The medic understood There are
ребята Нет там достаточно Медика понял
so many medics that they cover all the
Медиков столько что закрывают все
needs,
потребности
look, I saw Yes, I saw
осмотрите вот я видел Да я видел
telegram channels there for a few
телеграм-каналы там за несколько
you think I will,
ты думаешь я буду
I saw what your unit can
я видел что себе в подразделение может
let’s go  we will bring you went after all
давайте мы сведем вы поехали все-таки
Well, well, you think so, let's think
Ну хорошо из так считаешь давай подумаем
about it,
об этом
you say Why not, look at Afonov
говоришь А почему нет смотрите афонова
For  what I understand that this is a very layer
Для чего я понимаю что это очень слой
no it turns out that you understand what you are
нет получается что ты понимаешь о чем ты
talking about What you say that the doctors do not
говоришь Что ты говоришь что медикам не
need I say it is necessary I saw people
нужно Я говорю нужно я увидел люди
here I am ready Look I am ready I am ready to find
вот я готов Смотри я готов Я готов найти
you the units that you need
тебе подразделения в которые нужно
Medics will go ready for me to find the
Медика пойдешь готов мне найти
units must  go Seriously
подразделения должен пойти Ты серьезно
now seriously Well, yes Well, look You
сейчас серьезно Ну да Ну смотри Ты же
support the war in Ukraine,
поддерживаешь войну в Украине
there are a lot of rest for your guys because
там куча отдохнет ваших ребят из-за того
we don’t have timely medical
что нету своевременной медицинской
care.
помощи
I understand that you won’t
у нас не получится Я понимаю что не
go there like doctors like in Donetsk
пойдёшь туда типа медикам типа в Донецке
there are guys
есть ребята так
looking for their own doctors  the subdivision of the
ищут Медиков свое подразделение
subdivision everyone has already left there
подразделения туда уже все выехали еще
again, look I’m ready I’ll
раз вот смотрите Я готов Я тебе еще раз
explain to you again I’m ready personally Let’s get
объясняю я готов лично Давайте свести я
it together I’ll find in the telegram where they were looking for
вот найду в телеграме где они вот искали
publicly and we’ll guide you so that you
публично и вас ведем так чтобы вы
go personally to the doctors there
поехали поехали лично медикам туда
It’s okay if I need me without
Всё нормально если мне нужно я без тебя
you you won't go
вы вы не поедете
I'll tell you again I understood
я тебе ещё раз я понял
I understood everything absolutely understood Yes
я всё понял абсолютно понял Да
I understood I just wanted to understand Yes,
я понял Я просто хотел понять Да
how ready are you to go to  to
насколько ты готов ехать в чужую страну
help doctors save a foreign country to fight. Guys,
помогать воевать медикам спасать Ребята
yes, it turns out that it turns out that you are not
да получается Что получается что ты не
ready, you say that there are enough
готов ты говоришь что там хватает
Medics
Медиков
2-3 units to find which
2-3 подразделения найти которым нужно
Ukrainian you need to throw some kind of nation on the nation, you
украинская вы на нацию какую-то
know why The fact is that all such
знаете почему Дело в том что все такие
Nazis are brave somewhere  then in Tula in
нацисты они смелые где-то в Туле в Туле
Tula they sit on the seats on the perch
на сидении на сидушки сидят на жердочке
already,
уже
but because you won’t
а потому что Приехать Приехать вы не
be
сможете
able to come to come you want to support the war in a
вы хотите поддерживать войну в чужой
foreign country with proxy
стране чужими руками
you want some other guy to
Вы хотите чтобы какой-то другой парень
go to Donetsk and they kill him there they do
ехал в донецку и его там убили они вас
n’t want you
не хотите
[  laughter] in
[смех]
short, a doctor Yes, I support on sv blah
короче медик Да я поддерживаю на св бла
blah like
бла типа
I want to eat people all these are for patriots, that's
хочу есть народ все эти за патриоты вот
what you are waiting for You wanted war in
Чего вы ждете Вы же хотели войны в
Ukraine from Ukraine, bring everything to Ukraine
Украине с Украины все Валите в Украину
Why mobilize ordinary people
Зачем мобилизировать простых людей
who do not want do not want to go to war
которые не хотят не хотят идти на войну
And you  you want for this war, you
А вы же хотите вы за эту войну вы ее
support it, you ignited it for 8 years Yes,
поддержите вы зажигали вы 8 лет Да вот
you rocked it all
это все раскачивали
and now support them don’t go at all
и теперь поддерживайте их вообще не
yes don’t need Medics Dude I’m
идете да не надо Медиков Чувак я вот
all Russians  to which they say that it’s
всем всем русским до которые говорят что
not this Medic lacks machine gunners ready
не это Медика хватает пулеметчиков готов
to bring you down as
вас свести
terrorists so that you are there Medics
террористами чтобы вы были там Медиков
don’t whistle here on the Internet it’s
не свистели тут в интернете
one thing to sit in Tula in Tula on a chair
одно дело сидеть в Туле в Туле на стуле
and everywhere to
и везде
all subscribers that you’re there, in short,
всем подписчикам что типа ты там короче
there’s something fashionable dude and the other
что-то там модный чувак а другой
answer  for your bazaar if you
отвечать за свой базар если ты
support a war in a foreign country, that
поддерживаешь войну в чужой стране то
is, they said that I have a category B of the
есть они говорили что у меня категория Б
type, let others send to a foreign
типа пусть других отправляет в чужую
country for war And I
страну на войну А я короче
don’t need doctors in
медикам не нужно
short  you are
пишите свои комментарии Как вы
characterized by their funny characters And
характеризуется их смешных персонажей А
we where the models of the shovel squeezed and
мы куда модели лопаты тискал и
prefer per kilo in the field
предпочтите на килограмм в области